all my girls
come on yeah
cut it out skip talk
let me see you get it done with the guts (with the guts)
if it’s meaningless Imma crop (Imma crop)
you know I don’t give a what, gotta hunt
gotta hunt yeah
standing on skid zone
I don’t wanna turn away I better speed up
wanna slide going far more higher (higher)
ready for my life (ready for my life)
feeling weak いらない いらない
shatter that trauma (no cap)
take it or leave it (like that)
want it? Then get it (on track)
all set
lip gloss make ’em fuss cause
Imma make it work
your doubt get ‘em cut cause
better work work work work
work work work
keep on gotta run
I know I better work
Imma make it work that (work work it)
know I better work (work)
Imma do it my way (work work it)
know I better work
put off until when I wanna do it
run away to dodge a bullet
but you know what señorita?
I don’t care being myself
you don’t know me it is real
little freckle even slick
if I do it, it’s a kick
when I do it let ‘em know it like this
stepping one stepping two keep
do you see the wound, wait for the twist
baby I can become anything SEE
like that push it back
push it back like this
now
now get back to my race
the more I’m cut I get more worthy feeling like a jewel
like a jewel
Nada
I never fix
make ’em move make ’em prove
that’s my style
lip gloss make ’em fuss cause
Imma make it work
your doubt get ‘em cut cause
better work work work work
work work work
keep on gotta run
I know I better work
Imma make it work that
know I better work
Imma do it my way (work work it)
Imma make it work that (work work it)
know I better work
risky but it’s worth it (work work it)
yeah I love all my flaws
vaulting over the wall
across the limit line
go further more jump
well I do what I do
hands full but want it more
I know that it’s time for us
lip gloss make ’em shock cause
Imma make it work
trash talk make ‘em hush cause
better work work work work
work work work
step up gotta run
I know I better work
Imma make it work that
know I better work that (work work that)
Imma do it my way
know I better work